You're supposed to call me Yoshino, remember?
Why would I have a
nonsensical dream like that?
Nope, not happening!
Absolutely not!
Gâteau au Chocolat Cake
The real deal!
Truffle Chocolates
How to make them on page 36
Hey, these are cute!
I guess we could make chocolate cake, too.
I prefer nama chocolates myself.
What do you think, Kojuurou-kun?
Feature on Homemade
Valentine's Chocolates
Cakes with whipping cream in them
taste great, but don't keep very long.
They might be hard to take to class.
Oh, that's right!
There has to be a good idea somewhere.
That's rare. Kojuurou's popular with the girls.
Kojuurou-sama is considered
a savior to troubled girls.
A savior?
Oh, morning, you two!
What are you all talking about? Seems fun.
Absolutely not! This is a very
serious strategy meeting.
Strategy meeting?
The real deal!
Truffle Chocolates
Perfect for buzzworthy pictures
Lollipop Chocolates
Gâteau au Chocolat Cake
Feature on Homemade
Valentine's Chocolates
Super-rich Gâteau
au Chocolat
Easy Chocolate Muffins
We're getting ready for Valentine's Day!
Valentine's Day?
Yup! Valentine's Day!
Ah... you act early.
#9 "Saint Valentine Is Watching"
Failure is not an option, so we've asked
the Sweets Shogun to act as our consultant.
Makabe-kun! They actually need me!
Do I look manly?
W-Well, I definitely think they trust you...
Though it's pretty obvious that
they just see you as one of them...
You'll be getting some from me,
too, so look forward to it.
Actually, do you have any requests?
Huh? N-No, I'm...
I'm interested because it shows who's
popular, but I don't want any sweets...
Oh, I guess you'd be getting
some from Adagaki-san.
I guess I shouldn't butt in.
R-Right...
The ones from Shop A
have black tea syrup inside.
The ones from Shop B are almond-flavored.
Shop C seemed very proud of
how good their cacao is.
Then I guess I'll start with Shop A.
Hmm... I wish they had more depth.
More depth desired.
You said the next ones are almond-flavored,
right? Do you want to try them?
Aki-sama...
Is this a rehearsal for Valentine's Day?
Wh-Wh-What are you talking about?
These are just snacks for me!
I'm getting my carbs!
"Getting your carbs"...
That's right! I'm not falling for
this "Valentine's Day" nonsense!
Why don't you try making homemade chocolates?
Are you even listening to me?
Well, I'm sure it would make him happy.
Why are you like this?
He'll just laugh at me if I can't
make something proper.
Don't worry. I'll teach you how to make them.
You've got this.
Hmph! This is easy as pie!
Hot!
Maybe I should get Japanese-style
matcha chocolates for Fujinomiya-san...
Wait, would it be weird
for me to give them to her?
Ingredients for 3 muffins
Butter (Margarine is also OK!) 45g
Chocolate 60g A little more than 1 bar of chocolate
Sugar 25g
Cocoa Powder 10g
I didn't make enough last year,
so I need to make more
Obligatory chocolates 25
Friendship chocolates 25
Chocolates for me 5
(for tasting!)
Make around 60??
20x more!!
Okay, I've got the recipe down.
If we split up the cost of
the ingredients three ways...
That's over budget!
Onii-chan!
Try these!
Huh? Chocolates?
I'm gonna give them to my friends tomorrow.
Tell me if you think they're good or not.
Nope!
Aw, come on! One won't hurt.
Yes, it will.
Do you know how many kilometers I'd have to run
just to burn off the calories in one of those?
What, so even if you get chocolates on
Valentine's Day, you won't eat them?
That girl who came over that one time
might be making some for you.
And yet you're gonna say, "I don't want
any sweets because they'll make me fat"?
You're the worst!
I didn't say I'd do that!
Then you'll eat them, right?
They're finished!
It's the day before,
but I somehow made it in time!
I'm glad we abandoned the nama
chocolate route and went for cookies.
Yes.
Yes, these are perfectly scrumptious.
Want some?
No, I'm going to clean up.
I see.
Hey, you're not going to give anyone any?
Huh?
You know, even if you don't have
someone particular in mind,
you can give out obligatory chocolates.
There are some who wouldn't enjoy getting them.
Well, I guess you're right.
Not everyone likes chocolate, after all.
Happy Valentine's Day!
Yes!
It's time for Tae's annual chocolates!
Is this one just for me?
They're obligatory, dummy.
I'll still take them!
Fire Hydrant
Calm down. Just be casual.
Okay!
F-Fujinomiya-san!
Oh, Kojuurou-sama.
Um, here you go... if you want.
Oh, my. This is the first time a
gentleman has given me chocolates.
I-It is weird, isn't it?! I'm sorry!
Not at all. I'm delighted.
Thank you very much.
Oh? Aki-sama.
You two sure seem close.
Huh?! Th-Th-Th-That's not true!
Look. Kojuurou-sama gave me these.
Hey, not bad.
Of course, you're giving some to
Masamune-sama, aren't you, Aki-sama?
Huh?! That's none of your business!
There's no need to be embarrassed.
Valentine's Day is the number one
event for couples, after all.
W-Well, I'm his girlfriend,
so of course I'm giving him chocolates.
Indeed. I'm glad you seem to
be enjoying your romance.
Yeah...
Let's go, Yoshino.
Right.
Makabe-senpai! Please take these!
Oh, you're the girl from the other day.
You remembered me! Oh, I'm so flattered!
I'm still cherishing the
empty bottle you gave me!
Huh?!
I'm ready whenever you want to
take our relationship to the next level!
I'll be waiting for you, Senpai!
Yeah, she's pretty bizarre...
But still...
I can't believe I got all these in a single day.
Message
Cruel Princess
Edit
Come to the gym
storage.
Cruel Princess
Could this be...
Adagaki-san!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Well... That's quite the haul.
Huh? Ah, uh... yeah...
Those are definitely the Cruel Princess's eyes.
I'm sorry! These are, uh...
I guess you don't need any from me
if you already have that many.
Huh?
That's not true!
If you made chocolates,
I'd love to have them!
Truly, from the bottom of my heart.
You don't need to flatter me.
I'm not!
Then... here.
Did you burn yourself?
You don't need to notice that!
How could I betray her?
Do you mind if I eat these right now?
Huh? R-Right now?!
I'm super hungry.
My diet...
My regimen...
My physical makeover...
My eight years' worth of wanting revenge...
Needing to be the hot guy...
Throw all of that away!
Yeah! They're super delicious,
Aki-chan!
Crap! I overslept!
Arriving ten minutes early
is an absolute must for dates!
Huh?!
She's already here?!
I'm so sorry, Adagaki-san!
You don't need to apologize. You're not late.
Thanks. But you're pretty early.
Were you that excited? Just kidding.
Huh?
Sh-She's so cu—
Anyway! You came here hungry, didn't you?
Of course! This whole date is about
eating while we walk around.
Will you be able to keep up
with me until the end?
I can't have you underestimating my stomach.
First, we're going to be
eating super-fluffy bread,
then we're going to have lunch at
Super Yummy Burgers, and then...
Could we get three more of
those super-fluffy breads?
Should you really go that
hard right from the start?
Yes. The bread's amazing,
but this omelet you can only get in
the mornings is also incredibly good!
I'd like some more, too, please! Three more!
Hey, did you hear?
Onii-chan's on a date
with his girlfriend today.
Yes, I know. I was so surprised!
To think that narcissist brother of mine
could actually get a girlfriend.
Well, Maa-kun's changed lately.
When I'd make him sweets before,
he'd never eat them.
But two days ago, he ate a whole cream puff!
Actually, he's been
eating more lately in general.
He was fussing about not wanting to
eat chocolate just the other day.
Is this all...
...thanks to his girlfriend?!
Aw... I can't wait to meet
Maa-kun's girlfriend!
Right?
Can I get a triple Super Yummy Burger meal,
two sweet and hot nuggets,
and two custard pies?
Sure.
What about you, Makabe?
Let's see...
Sides
French Fries
Chicken
Sweet and Hot
Custard Pie
Apple Pie
Soft Drinks
Single Drinks
Crap. I ate too much bread,
and I'm already full.
You're probably full, aren't you?
Don't push yourself.
Why don't you just get a drink?
No, I'll order something.
My goal today is to share
delicious things with you.
I'd like a Super Yummy Burger meal,
please. With a double patty.
See? I told you.
I admit defeat.
But we just finished lunch...
I'm so sorry.
I'm really happy, though.
Um, hang on just a sec.
If I exercise a bit, I'll be hungry again.
You idiot! If you do that...
Two, three, four, five...
Honestly... Here, have some water.
Nature's Bounty
Natural Water
Th-Thanks.
Sorry you had to see me being so pathetic.
I haven't been this full since I was a kid.
Well, you did eat a lot back then.
Yeah, I definitely have the potential.
So just give me a little more time.
You're such an idiot.
Sorry... I ended up not being able
to eat anything after that.
Don't worry about it.
I got to eat everything I wanted to,
and I figured something
like this would happen.
I'm kidding.
I had a lot of fun.
See you later.
Adagaki-san!
Let's go on another date. We can
wander around and eat again or whatever!
Yes, let's.
Hey, what do you want to do over spring break?
You're already in spring break mode?
Well, exams are over, so why not?
Oh, you're all alone?
So are you.
Since we're both alone, do you mind
if I have a seat next to you?
Go ahead.
Where's Aki-sama?
Probably with Makabe.
Are things going well with them?
Probably. They've been
going on a lot of dates lately.
I see... And you're not lonely?
What?
You've always been attached
at the hip with Aki-sama,
and now you have less time with her.
That's true...
But I just want Aki-sama to be happy.
You two have a beautiful friendship.
I also want Aki-sama and
Masamune-sama to be happy.
I found a hamburger shop
yesterday that I think you'd like.
Wanna go sometime?
Hamburgers... Not a bad idea.
Yes! It'll definitely be good.
Apparently, they use the perfect
balance of beef and pork there.
Okay, Mr. Gourmand.
Yup. I keep finding myself
looking for delicious places.
But I'll be fine because I'm still exercising.
I don't want to go back to how I used to look.
I see.
Whoa!
Makabe?!
Ow...
Are you okay?
W-Workout opportunity!
Well? Wasn't that amazing?
S-Sure...
Okay, let's go.
Masamune-sama.
This is yours, isn't it?
You forgot it in the last class.
Oh, how careless of me.
It's snowing outside?
Yikes, looks like it's gonna stick.
Have you gotten a bit rounder?
Hm... Maybe.
I've been going along with Adagaki-san
on her food pilgrimages lately.
Oh, have you?
Yeah.
By the way, how have
things been with your hives?
I've been quite worried.
Oh, yeah. I'm totally fine now.
Really? If it happens again,
you should go to the hospital.
No, really. I'm fine!
Thanks, though.
And I mean, you don't die
from hives, so I'll be fine.
Where's Aki-sama today?
She had something to do, apparently.
Maybe I'll head home before
the snow starts piling up.
Indeed.
Why is it so dark?
Why would anyone put the
projector in the cafeteria?
Why did I have to be on
class duty today of all days?
I'm here.
I'm terribly sorry to ask you to
meet me in this cold weather.
I'm honestly more worried about you.
I couldn't sleep knowing you caught a cold
because you refuse to wear underwear.
You're so kind, Aki-sama.
What do you want?
I ask this from the bottom of my heart.
I know I have no right to ask this,
but still...
Still...
I must ask that you break up
with Masamune-sama.
Lift your head.
There's no way I'd agree to that.
Masamune-sama doesn't love you!
His heart lies elsewhere,
but he's tied down by his past feelings,
and he's in so much pain right now.
That's just...
I already know that, okay?!
I know that.
I saw his planner a while back.
What is this? A revenge planner?
In it were various ways to get me to fall
for him, because he hated me so much.
I see.
But if you knew, then why didn't you...
Because...
I love him, of course!
At first, I absolutely couldn't believe it.
I figured he casually showed interest in me
because he was so confident about his looks.
He works so hard at being an idiot.
That's just...
You could say he just works stupidly hard,
but when he thinks I don't like him, he panics.
He gets mad if I'm a bit cold.
I couldn't figure out why
he wouldn't just give up.
I was so curious...
Actually, when I found out he was
the Masamune from the past...
I was so happy.
Aki-sama...
There were a lot of things I noticed
once we started going out, too...
But it all makes sense
if he actually doesn't like
I'm going to get revenge
on that woman!!
the past me or the present me.
I can't understand why you feel this way!
How can you say that you
love Masamune-sama, then?
Did you know?
He used to be a bit weird and different, too.
Even if he dislikes me or denies me,
I won't let Masamune go now.
Because...
that's just who I am.
So... I'm in the same boat as you.
Our feelings only go one way.
I think my feelings might be
more deeply rooted, though.
Kojuurou-sama...
Oh, s-sorry!